[{
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following items was owned by the fewest U.S homes in 1990?",
        "answers": [
            "home Computer",
            "compact disk player",
            "cordless phone",
            "dishwater"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "In 1990, in what percentage of U.S married couples did the wife earn more money than the husband?",
        "answers": ["8", "18", "38", "58"]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "The first black American pictured on a U.S postage stamp was who?",
        "answers": [
            "Frederick Douglass",
            "Booker T. Washington",
            "Louis Armstrong",
            "Joe Louis"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What did the 'D' in 'D-Day' stand for?",
        "answers": ["doom", "day", "Dwight", "Dunkirk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "which of the following characters turned 40 years old in 1990?",
        "answers": ["Charlie Brown", "Bugs Bunny", "Mickey Mouse", "Fred Flintstone"]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The Philadelphia mint started putting a 'P' mint maek on quarters when ?",
        "answers": ["1960", "1980", "never", "1958"]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "In J.Edgar Hoover, what did the J stand for?",
        "answers": ["James", "John", "Joseph", "Jack"]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "When did the Liberty bell get its name?",
        "answers": [
            "when it was made in 1701",
            "when it rang on July 4, 1776",
            "in the 19th century, whent it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery",
            "none"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Cleromancy is divination involving what?",
        "answers": ["Dice", "Glass", "Twigs", "Ink"]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "A person who's a fysigunkuus lacks what?",
        "answers": ["Humor", "Wisdom", "Curiosity", "Temper"]
    }
]